inma.org 2019-06-24

# None

Your privacy is important to INMA. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that INMA collects, and the ways in which INMA uses that personal information. INMA is the trade name of the International News Media Association which is incorporated in the Commonwealth of Virginia and does business in the State of Texas, both in the United States. We can be reached by telephone at +1 214 373-9111.

## Personal information collection

INMA may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * Information about your use of this Web site.
  * Information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the Web site.
  * Information about transactions carried out over this Web site.
  * Information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the Web site services.
  * Any other information that you send to INMA, including:
    * Name
    * Job title
    * Company
    * Email
    * Telephone number

## Using personal information

INMA may use your personal information to:

  * Administer this Web site.
  * Personalise the Web site for you.
  * Enable your access to and use of the Web site services.
  * Publish information about you on the Web site.
  * Send to you products that you purchase.
  * Supply to you services that you purchase.
  * Send you statements and invoices.
  * Collect payments from you.
  * Send you marketing communications.

Where INMA discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, INMA may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise, or defend its legal rights.

## Cookies

We use cookies (information stored by your browser) to track information on the pages read by visitors to the Web site to improve the content and offerings on the Web site. INMA.org uses cookies to identify members when they sign-in to the site.

Although we cannot identify individuals from this information, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. Cookies can be disabled on your computer, but this may limit the experience that our Web site is able to offer.

Third Party cookies may include:

  * Anonymous tracking for analytic purposes via Google
  * YouTube (embedded content)
  * Facebook (embedded content)
  * Twitter (embedded content)

## Securing of your data

INMA will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse, or alteration of your personal information. INMA will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers. Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this Web site will be protected by encryption technology.

## Updating this statement

INMA may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this Web site. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

## Inapplicability of Privacy Policies of Any Linked Websites or Other Third Parties

This Web site contains links to many other sites. However, INMA is not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites.

This Privacy Policy only addresses INMAâ€™s use and disclosure of your Personal Data. The Web site may contain links to other Web sites, be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites, and we are not liable for their misuse of Personal Data. When you visit another Web site you should carefully read that siteâ€™s privacy policy.

## Children

This Web site is not intended for use by or targeted at children under 13, and we do not knowingly or intentionally collect information about children under 13.

## Contact INMA

If you have questions about this privacy policy or INMA's treatment of your personal information, please contact us by telephone at +1 214 373-9111 or by mail/post at P.O. Box 740186, Dallas, Texas 75374, United States.
